Job hunting means the same work over and over. Finding the postings. Reading them properly.
Working out whether you're actually a fit. DevJobInfo does that part for you.
Everything lands on one dashboard.
How many jobs came in, how well they match you, and how many applications you've sent this week.
Underneath, your pipeline by stage — saved, applied, interviewing, and the ones that have gone quiet.
Plus how your match scores are spread, so you can see whether you're aiming at the right roles.
It all rests on your profile. This is what every job gets scored against.
Drop in your CV and it fills itself in — skills, experience, education, the lot.
From there you can adjust anything. The more accurate this is, the more honest the scoring gets.
Search five job boards at once — one query instead of five tabs.
Or paste a URL straight in, and it'll pull the posting apart for you.
Postings in any language work as they are. A Danish job stays in Danish — nothing gets translated behind your back.
Every job comes back scored from nought to a hundred against your profile.
When a posting is too thin to judge fairly, it caps the score instead of pretending otherwise.
Open any job for the full reasoning.
Which skills matched, which are missing, and why it landed there.
Experience and seniority score separately, so a skills match can't mask a role that's too junior.
From here, a cover letter — written from your actual history.
In the language of the posting, so a Danish job gets a Danish letter.
And nothing invented. No companies you didn't work for, no projects you didn't build. Only what's in your profile.
Then a resume tailored to this specific role.
Same career, reordered around what this employer actually asked for — the relevant work first, the rest still there.
Both download as PDFs, ready to send.
Find the jobs. Research the companies. Land the role.
DevJobInfo — devjob.info